If...
If I had one more chance...
A hospital?
My arm's intact.
My legs, too.
I was stabbed through the chest,
but there's no trace of it.
Was it just... a dream?
Oh, I see you're awake.
Excuse me...
I'm Woo Jinchul, manager of the
Hunter's Association Surveillance Team.
I'm Kang Taeshik.
What's someone from
Surveillance want with me?
For now, let's get your doctor in here.
I was unconscious for three days?
What about Joohee and Mr. Song?
Are they okay?
Yes. Although...
Song Chiyul lost an arm, and as a result,
he may have to retire as a hunter.
And Lee Joohee's been traumatized.
She's undergoing psychiatric care.
Given her condition, I'm not sure
she'll continue as a hunter, either.
There were only six survivors of the double
dungeon discovered on your expedition.
A hunter's job is always a dangerous one,
but it's rare to see such a tragic outcome.
And yet, somehow,
when the White Tiger Guild arrived on the
scene after being alerted by the survivors,
all they found was you, Sung Jinwoo,
collapsed on the ground.
There were no traces of the temple or
the statues the survivors described.
But that's...
Unbelievable, isn't it?
If there had been the slightest
inconsistency between their reports,
or if some of the deceased's remains
hadn't been found on the scene,
it would've cast suspicion
onto your group instead.
Incidentally...
This is just speculation on our part, but...
Sung Jinwoo...
Have you experienced a second awakening?
A second awakening?
A hunter's power is determined upon awakening,
and it never changes from that point on.
But... on rare occasions, a hunter
can go through a second awakening.
It lets them exceed their previous limits
and rise to A or even S-Rank...
Maybe I could, too!
This is a mana meter.
Please place your hand over it.
If they really ran into instakill-level
magic beasts, like the survivors said,
then there's no way a low-level hunter
could have survived.
And for not even a trace
to remain of said beasts
would imply the presence of an A-Rank—
maybe even S-Rank hunter.
The most likely explanation is that
Sung Jinwoo underwent a second awakening.
What's it say?!
If I've awakened again,
what rank does it put me at now?
My apologies. I'm afraid we
may have been mistaken.
Even E-Ranks usually manage higher than 70...
He's basically just a civilian.
The dungeon has vanished
and can't be explored again.
So how did he survive?
Aw, man. I got my hopes up.
And I can't help but wonder why
they didn't ask about this thing.
Maybe I'm the only one who can see it?
So it's not a touch panel, then.
I remember something like this
popping up before, too.
Jinah?
You need to take better care of yourself!
Do you know how worried I was?!
Sorry...
You always end up a mess,
even when everyone else is fine!
I get worried, okay?!
I can't believe I was prepared
to leave her behind.
You were out for three whole days this time!
What are you smiling about?
The next time something like this happens,
I'm gonna quit school and get a job
so you don't have to be a hunter anymore!
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
But, Jinah... Can you see this?
See what?
Never mind. Sorry.
Listen... You know how sometimes in a game,
it says you have unread notifications?
We're talking about games now?
How do you manage to read them, usually?
Should they be examining your head, too?
Jinah, you used to play games
all the time, remember?
I mean, sure. You'd usually
open your message box, right?
Open the message box...
Why bring up games all of a sudden?
Well, y'know, not a lot to do in a hospital.
I remember this "Player" stuff
being mentioned before...
Well, you seem fine, at least.
I oughta go.
Sorry about the wait, Song-yi.
"This system is designed to assist
the development of the Player."
"Failure to comply with the system
may result in a penalty..."
"The rewards have been delivered"?
I don't have a clue what
this is supposed to mean.
"Daily Quest: Strength Training."
Confirm.
Push-ups, sit-ups, squats, running...
"Failure to complete the daily quest
will result in an appropriate penalty"?
What the hell?
If this is a joke, I'm not laughing.
I'm hospitalized. Where am I gonna
get that kind of stamina?
What in the world is going on?
Regarding that hunter, Sung Jinwoo...
It doesn't appear he's had
a second awakening, Chairman Go.
I see.
We're lucky this incident didn't result in a
dungeon break, but something about it...
It leaves too many unanswered questions.
Right. It's nothing like any previous case.
Even allowing for how dungeons
tend to be full of mysteries....
I think this'll need to be
marked as a special case
and entered into the databank
for further evaluation.
Understood.
It's gonna be a long day.
I'd like you to participate in the next
B-Rank raid as an instructor, Miss Cha.
As an instructor?
This raid is going to serve as a test
and practical training for new recruits.
Can you handle it?
I have doubts about my ability as a mentor.
All you need to do is fight
how you normally do.
Everyone will learn from your example.
That's just how talented you are.
The Hunters Guild is one of
the five largest guilds in the country,
but on an international level,
we're unremarkable.
And while individual ranks can't be increased,
our collective combat ability can be honed,
so that we'll be ready when the time comes.
Another gate?
In the middle of the damn road, too.
When are the hunters gonna show up?
I wish they'd take care of it already.
A-An earthquake?!
A... desert? What is happening?
Am I dreaming? I was just in the hospital—
Are you... kidding me?!
Huh?
Is something wrong?
The patient from this room...
How many of them are there, damn it?!
Two more hours of this?!
Any sign of him?
No. Not where I looked.
I think I'll check the room again.
Good idea.
I doubt he left the hospital...
Can't... keep running...
A penalty... quest?
Mr. Sung?!
Mr. Sung, are you all right?!
Yeah, I'm healing nicely.
I should be able to leave soon.
That's a relief.
After all the worry you caused me,
I'm expecting to be treated at Chagall.
Okay, okay, sure.
All right, time to go.
You want me... for a raid?
Yes. A D-Rank gate appeared
in Hapjeong the other day,
and all the guilds have prior engagements.
I understand if you can't, of course.
We understand what you've
been through, Hunter Lee.
I'm sorry.
No apologies necessary.
Oh, that said, I heard that
Sung Jinwoo has woken up.
He has?!
Jinwoo... He's okay. That's wonderful!
Look. He's running again.
Honestly... He's been at it every day
since regaining consciousness.
Jinwoo...
I know hunters are supposed to heal
faster than normal people, but...
He says he's trying to get back into shape.
And he doesn't listen when
we tell him to take it easy.
Even though he was badly
injured just a few days ago.
He's a real handful.
It's been four days since
I regained consciousness.
I've figured out a few things.
First, I'm not hallucinating these windows.
When I complete the daily quest,
I get three types of rewards.
Full recovery.
All that exhaustion is gone in a flash.
Next is the ability points.
I can distribute the points
into whatever abilities I choose.
I should probably go with strength, right?
Upgrading my abilities makes me
that much more powerful.
I can literally tell that
I've got more strength now.
I've also got these skill
and inventory screens.
My world's taken a real turn
for the strange.
It's like a game!
And my final daily quest reward...
the random loot box.
I wonder what it'll be today?
A key?
I've only gotten useless stuff like
pens and bandages so far...
An instance dungeon? What's that?
Based on what's happened so far, it'll be
some kind of event to help me get stronger...
And now a report on today's gate conditions.
New D-Rank gates have appeared at these locations.
The C-Rank gates in the Upper East and
Midtown areas are currently being dealt with.
The B-Rank gate that appeared
in the wharf district the other day
is scheduled to be raided within
a few days by the Hunters Guild.
Expect traffic delays as a result.
That was a really long line, huh?
It's supposed to be for sweets.
Understood. I'll head back to the office.
Mom!
Mom, wake up!
What happened?!
It's Mom... She won't respond!
Eternal Sleep Disease?
It's also known as Final Rest.
It's a disease that came into existence
with the appearance of the gates.
It affects roughly one in every
several ten thousand people.
There are theories that it's caused
by continual exposure to mana.
In any case, the best that modern
medicine can provide is life support.
All right, kiddo!
Step lively now!
Right!
Congratulations.
You qualify to become a hunter.
We're looking forward to
seeing what you can do.
I did it, Jinah! Now I can
afford Mom's treatment!
Isn't it dangerous, though?
It'll be okay. Just leave it to me.
What're you doing?!
Just sit in a corner and don't do anything!
Damned E-Rank, slowing us down...
And for the record, if you don't
contribute, you don't get a cut!
I'm sorry for being so useless.
I'll put my ability points into strength.
I've got my gear ready.
I've taken care of everything.
And I'm confident that I can
run away if I need to.
If things get dangerous, like last time,
I'll get the hell out of there.
No!
The exit's been sealed off?
I see. So I'm in a separate dimension.
Instance dungeons aren't
like the regular kind...
I've never been into one myself,
but I bet they're like red gates.
What a mess. I was thinking
I could run, if I had to...
But that's out now.
"Teleportation stone"?
What's that? I guess I'm stuck here
until I can clear the dungeon?
I couldn't even beat E-Rank beasts before.
And now I have to clear a dungeon by myself?
That's crazy...
Can I really beat a boss without any party?
Still, I don't have a choice!
What do I do? I'm suddenly
feeling less confident.
Here they come! And there's three!
I beat one...
I've gotten stronger.
A wolf.
I can sense it...
This one's way stronger than those goblins.
My legs... won't move!
Why?!
Am I afraid?
I didn't think I was traumatized...
Damn it!
There's no healer with me!
If I get injured here, I'm done for!